Guide to the Board of Trustees records, 1821-2003 RG0001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Committees, 1911-1960; RG0001 Series 5; 4 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8)
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 03/06/1956 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Text on folder "Report on the Old Fire House and the Association of Oldest Inhabitants.; Discussion relative to purchase of Allen Lee Hotel, 2224 F Street, Lots 9 and 10 in Square 58, to house new government contracts; Action was deferred until special meeting ot the Board. Freeway proposal discussion, consideration deferred until later; Possibility of construction of building on Square 56 for additional research contracts and to free Building D for use as Law Library; Committee on the University Hospital report relative to additional space in the Hospital if the Ford Foundation grant is received. Voted to recommend this to the Board of Trustees; Discussion relative to purchase of the property at corner of 20th and H Sts. which had been considered earlier. Consideration deferred until later."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 02/16/1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Text on folder "Urban Renewal Project discussion with special reference to the proposed inner belt freeway which would pass through Squares 41 and 42. It was agreed that President Marvin should write a statement concerning thought of the Committee and proper timing of any steps that might be taken, to be presented to Committee at its next meeting. This matter was brought up at request of Trustee Glover; Discussion about whether or not Univ. should buy property in the area at this time prior to decision about the Urban Renewal Project. To check with Redevelopment Land Agency about its attitude."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 10/04/1955 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Text on folder "Resolution for purchase of Lot 811 in Square 42, 2318 H Street, N.W. The George Washington University Urban Renewal Project discussion. Recommendations: Board express appreciation to D.C. Redevelopment Land Agency and National Capital Planning Commission; Board express desire to cooperate with these agencies; Board authorize President and Treasurer, with approval of Bldg. and Lands Committee, to employ an architect to prepare plan."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 05/17/1955 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Text on folder "Approval of plan to offer $10 per square foot for property in Square 40. Terms of payment for property in Square 40 outlined."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 05/05/1955 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Text on folder "Sale of National University property (Lots 14 and 15 in Square 286, known as 1225-27 New York Avenue) to Mr. Nick Papanicolas approved for recommendation to the Board; Letter from President Marvin regarding sale of property in Square 40 to the University. Independent appraisal authorized; Alterations in Hospital (Pathology Lab to provide for Blood Bank) and (rearrangement of rooms in Obstetrics and Gynecology for Dr. Parks) were approved."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 02/07/1955 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Text on folder "Sale of Lot 815 in Square 1234 (1310 29th Street, N.W.) - Approved; Purchase of following approved: Lot 810 in Square 101, 2017 H St., NW; Lot 19 in Square 55, 2217 H St., NW; Lot 831 in Square 101, 2010 I St. NW; Lot 841 in Square 77, 812 21st St. NW; Air Conditioning of Monroe Hall and School of Government; National University Property; Report on attempt to purchase 804 19th St.; Delay in Tompkins Hall of Engineering; Animals Runs for Clinic; Equipment move in Dept. of Radiology; Office Space in Out Patient Dept. remodeled for Dept. of Medicine; Changes in Old Hospital remodeling; Items to come up later: Student Union dining room enlargement, Erection of building for offices, Storage space for Dept. of Chemistry."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 11/30/1954 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Text on folder "Use of Lots 802, 25, and 26 in Square 41 for off-street parking for Tompkins Hall of Engineering. Covenant approved; Discussion re purchase of Lot 822 in Square 56; Razing of buildings on H Street front of Square 56; Trustee Tompkins increase to $750,000 of his gift for the Tompkins Hall of Engineering; National University property asking price approved. (Lots 14, 15 in Square 286); Robin Miller bequest property approved for placing on market. (Lot 815 in Square 1234); Offer to purchase 2010 Eye Street, N.W.; Properties approved for purchase consideration: Lot 810 in Square 101, 2017 H Street; Lot 22 in Square 119, 804 19th Street; Lot 19 in Square 77, 812 21st Street (for reappraisal first). Properties not approved for consideration: Lots 35 and 36, Square 79, 2144 H Street and 733 22nd Street; Lot 829 in Square 77, 2130 Eye Street; Lot 828 in Square 77, 2132 Eye Street; Lot 823 in Square 77, 2142 Eye Street; Lot 823 in Square 101, 823 21st Street; Lot 801 in Square 55, 804 22nd Street; Lot 814 in Square 77, 807 22nd Street; Lot 820 in Square 77, 821 22nd Street; Lot 806 in Square 42, 733 24th Street. Medical School building program discussion."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 10/18/1954 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Text on folder "Parking Facilities for Tompkins Hall of Engineering; Recommendation that lots on H Street Front of Square 41 between 23rd and 24th Streets be designated."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 10/07/1954 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Text on folder "Razing of improvements on following properties approved: 708 22nd Street (Square 56, Lot 23); 611-613 23rd Street (Square 57, Lots 822, 825); 2111 H Street, N.W. (Square 77, Lot 802); 2127 H Street, N.W. (Square 77, Lot 809); 2208 to 2224 H Street, N.W. (Square 56, Lots 14 to 19 inclusive; Lot 822 when acquired); Approval to purchase the following: 708 22nd Street (Square 56, Lot 23); 2125 H Street (Square 77, Lot 808); 2214 H Street (Square 56, Lot 18); 2218 H Street (Square 56, Lot 16); 2222 H Street (Square 56, Lot 14); Negotiate further purchase of 2017 H Street (Square 101, Lot 810); 2010 I Street (Square 101, Lot 831); Off-Street parking for Tompkins Hall of Engineering; Approval to place National University Property (Square 286, Lots 14 and 15) on market; Robin Miller Estate; Deeding land for Warwick Memorial Building to Home for Foundlings in accordance with agreement; Use of barracks raised by Public Housing Administration; Tax exemption of University parking lots; Report on remodeling the old Hospital."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 06/23/1954 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Text on folder "Consideration of purchase of Lots 14, 16, 18, and 822 in Square 56; Consideration of purchase of Lots 55, 56, 800 through 805 in Square 101. Decision to try for lower price and higher possible return as parking lot."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 03/12/1954 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Text on folder "Discussion of Re-zoning of strip between Virginia Avenue and H on 24th Street. No action advised; Discussion of proposal to sell house at 1310-29th Street; Sterling Ruffin Estate - lot in Washington, referred to Counsel; Airconditioning Monroe Hall and School of Government; Tax exemptions for University properties."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 02/02/1954 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Text on folder "Lot 819 in Square 40, Lot 806 in Square 42 - Decided against purchase; Discussion of School of Medicine Building Site; Financial Report of Hospital as it pertains to School of Medicine plans."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 01/08/1954 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Text on folder "Plans for regular scheduled meetings of the Committee; Purchase of Lot 818 in Square 40 (939 New Hampshire Ave., N.W.); Discussion of plans for air conditioning needs; Discussion of parking needs. Suggestion of ramp parking; Decision to postpone purchase of Lots 55, 56, 800 through 805 in Square 101 (20th & H, N.W.); Resignation of Trustee Grant as Secretary of the Committee; Discussion of the "E Street Bridge" Proposal as it affects the University"
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 10/27/1953 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Text on folder "Purchase of Lot 29 in Square 40 (910 - 23rd Street, N.W.); Purchase of Lot 810 in Square 77 (2135 H Street, N.W.); Decision not to purchase Lots 801 and 802 in Square 103; Discussion of method of finishing yard around Warwick Memorial Bldg.; Authorization to tear down house on Lot 813 in Square 40 (905 New Hampshire Avenue, N.W.); Discussion of Square 119."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 04/29/1953 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Text on folder "Purchase of property"
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 01/07/1953 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Text on folder "Cancer Clinic, Square 39 - approval of plan of layout; X-ray Clinic extension - authorized development of plans and necessary steps; Mellon Wing of Hospital - approved alterations for space for second floor offices; Square 56 and Engineering Building - authorized developmental plans."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 12/09/1952 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Text on folder "Overheating hospital rooms - approval for remedial measures; X-ray Clinic - approval of one-story addition; Parking at Hospital - opposed to use of east lawn; Cafeteria - discussion of expansion by roofing passage-way between 2127 G St. and cafeteria; Square 77, Lot 36 - Case 95 - 800 21st St., N.W. - disapproval of purchase; Square 103, lot 14 - Case 193 - 2028 G St., N.W. - decision not to recommend purchase at present; Square 79, lot 811 - Case 88 - 721 22nd St., N.W. - decision not to purchase at present price - acquisitions previously made in Square 79 for drill field for A.F.R.O.T.C. did not include this."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 05/07/1952 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Text on folder "Price of $300,000 considered for old Hospital and School of Medicine; Several Lots considered: 708 & 710 - 22nd St. (lots 22 and 23, sq. 56; 2170 - 2109 H Streets (lots 800, 801 and 803 Sq. 77); 721 22nd St. (lot 811, sq. 79); 920 - 23rd St. (lot 24, square 40); 2217 H Street (lot 19, sq. 55); 2212 and 2214 G Street (lots 817 and 816, sq. 57"
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 03/05/1952 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Text on folder "Discussion of funds between G.W.U. Cancer Clinic, Helen L. & Mary E. Warwick Memorial and Washington Home for Foundlings; Adjustment of taxes referred to Counsel; Claim for exemption on parking property taxation referred to counsel; Remodeling of Building D."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 01/04/1952 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Text on folder " President made full statement of the financial status of the University. Gradual liquidation of indebtedness of the Hospital to University; Measures for increasing parking space; Desirability of purchasing the Washington Gas Light Company's property; Offer of $32,500.00 for 1921 H St. (Lot 802 in Sq. 119); Offer of $20,000.00 for 719 - 22nd St. N.W. (Lot 810 in Sq. 79)"
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 10/05/1951 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Text on folder "Minutes of the Meeting, Oct. 5, 1951."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 04/04/1951 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Text on folder "Minutes of the Meeting, April 4, 1951."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 12/06/1950 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Text on folder "Minutes of the Meeting, December 6, 1950"
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 10/24/1950 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Text on folder "Minutes of the Meeting, October 24, 1950."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 06/05/1950 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Text on folder "Minutes of the Meeting, June 5, 1950."
  - Committee on Building Lands--correspondence and meeting minutes, 01/04/1950 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Text on folder "Minutes of the Meeting, January 4, 1950."
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 11/08/1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 08/03/1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 06/14/1949 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 12/07/1948 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 11/30/1948 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 08/05/1948 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 12/10/1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 10/06/1947 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 07/17/1947 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Text on folder "Authorization of study ventilating system in Lisner Auditorium. Case 53, 2316 H St., N.W. (Square 42, Lot 812), Case 52, 1907 H St., N.W. (Square 119, Lot 16), Case 51, 1814-16 G. St., N.W. (Square 142, Lot 9) W "The Wagner Apartments", Case 50, 2106 Eye Street, N.W. (Square 77, Lot 27), Case 49, 2132-34 Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W. (Square 75, Lot 23-24), Case 48, 814 22nd St., N.W. (Square 55, Lot 15) Raymond Apartments, Case 47, 1915 G St., N.W. (Square 120, Lot 40), Case 42, 921 ssnd St., N.W. (Square 75, Lot 821), Case 41, 2211 H St., N.W. (Square 55, Lot 16), Case 35, 817 24th St., N.W. (Square 41, Lot 33)"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 06/02/1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Text on folder "Case 24 (Columbia Hotel, 2125 G St., N.W. Lot 836 in Square 79), Case 36 (Everglades, 2223 H St., N.W., Square 555, Lot 806 to 811), Case 27 (2315 H St., N.W., Square 41, Lot 26), Case 39 (2130 Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W., Square 75, Lot 831), Case 42 (921 - 22nd St., N.W., Square 75, Lot 821), Case 43 (901 - 22ns St., N.W., Square 75, Lot 846), Case 44 (2138 Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W., Square 75, Lot 34), Case 45 (2000 H. St., N.W., Square 102, Lot 39), Case 46 (2034 G. St., N.W., Square 103, Lot 806)"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 05/05/1947 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Text on folder "Case 118, 2110 G. St., N.W. (Square 80, Lot 40), Case 25, 2300-2310 G. St., N.W., Case 27, 2315 H St., N.W. (Square 41, Lot 26), Case 30, 2006 G. St., N.W. (Square 103, Lot 25), Case, 817 24th St., N.W. (Square 41, Lot 33), Case 36, 2223 H St., N.W. (Square 55, Lots 806 to 811), Case 37, (Square 101, Lots 39, 40, and Square 77, Lot 803), Case 39, 2130 Pennsylvania Ave., N.W. (Square 75, Lot 831), Case 40, 2126 Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W. (Square 75, Lot 832), Case 42, 921 22nd St., N.W. (Square 75, Lot 821), Case 43, 901 22 St., N.W. (Sqaure 75, Lot 846), Case 44, 2138 Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W. (Square 75, Lot 34), Case 45, 2000 H St. N.W. (Square 102, Lot 39), Case 41, 2211 H. St., N.W. (Square 55, Lot 16), Case 24, 2125 G St., N.W. (Square 79, Lot 836)"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 04/07/1947 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Text on folder "Case 37 (Lots 39, 40 and 828 inSquare 101) and Case 38 (Lot 803 in Square 77), Case 36 (Lot 806 to 811, Square 55) 2223 H St., N.W., Case 35 (Lot 33, Square 41) 817 24th St., N.W., Case 34 (Lot 823, Square 40) 923 23rd St., N.W., Case 33 (Lots 88 and 809, Square 57) 2224 and 2226 G St., N.W., Case 24 (Lot 836, Square 79) 2125 G St., N.W., Case 32 (Lot 813, Square 77) 1921 G St., N.W., Case 31 (Lot F, Square 120) 1921 G St., N.W., Case 30 (Lot 25, Square 103) 2006 G. St., N.W."
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 02/11/1947 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Text on folder "Special meeting to consider fire in Presiden'ts Office, February 5, 1947. Considered three alternatives: a. Restoration of building at cost of $7, 500 b. Remodeling at $25,000 c. New building. Site suggested in (c) has much of preparation already there. Committee recommended (c) be adopted by Board of Trustees $8,000 offered for 822 22nd Street, Northwest (Lot 829 in Square 55) rejected by owner. Authorized $40,000 for #18, 2110 G Street, Northwest (Square 80, Lot 40)"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 02/03/1947 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Text on folder "#18. 2110 G Street, Northwest (Sqaure 80, Lot 40), #21. 816 23rd Street, Northwest (Square 41, Lot 29), #24. 2125 G Street, Northwest (Square 79, Lot 836), #26. 822 22nd Street, Northwest (Square 55, Lot 829), #27. 2315 H Street, Northwest (Square 41, Lot 26) Committe not interested in following: #19. 2029 F Street, Northwest (Square 103, Lot 803), #22. 2147 F Street, Northwest (Square 80, Lot 42), #23. 2036 Eye Street, Northwest (Square 101, Lot 826), #25. Square 43, Lots 819, 1818, 817, 816, 831, 832, 811, #28. 1909 G Street, Northwest (Square 120, Lot 37), #29. The Naples, 713-715 - 19th Street, Northwest (square 141, Lot 21)"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 12/02/1946 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Text on folder "$150,000 available for purchases; $111, 250 obligated to date. #15. Lots 800 and 801 in Square 42 offered for $45,000 approved 811 21st Street, N.W. (Lot 819 in Square 101) considered excessive at $25,000, #16. Wagar Apartments, 1814 G Street, N.W. (Lot 9 in Square 142) offer not to be made. Discussion of situtation in Sqares 101, 40, 41, 119, 31, 18, 8 and 9. Urgency acquiring following: Washington Gas Light Corporation (Squares 8, 9, 18 and 31), Mathey property (Square 119), Lots 40, 815 and 816 in Sqaure 80, Land not yet acquired in Squares 41 and 56. Mr Olmsted's visit and report."
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 10/29/1946 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 12/27/1945 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Text on folder "Adoption of resolution authorizing solicitation of funds for new hospital equipment. Consideration of employment of professional assistance in raising of funds. Appointment of the following committee to study fund-raising organizations: President Marvin, Trustees Erwin, Lawson, Dean Bloedorn. Consideration of amounts to be designated for providing private rooms - decision postponed until after Committee report is received."
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 08/17/1943 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 05/27/1943 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Text on folder "Mention of suite brought against the University by Alice Morrison. War [crossed out and replaced with word Water] damage insurance and increased for Auditorium. Proposed sale of property at 3213 Thirteenth Street (part of Paro Estate). Remodeling of Straughton Hall. Proposed purchase of property at 2208 H Street. Proposed purchase of property at 2135 G Street. Proposed purchase of property at Northwest corner of 20th and H Streets."
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 03/09/1943 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Text on folder "Sale of property at Germantown, Maryland. Purchase of Lot 813, Square, 2027 H Street, N.W. Need to spend more than the amount authorized for renovating Madeira Apartments at 707 Twenty-second Street, N.W. Recommendation of employment of Edwin Weihe as architect and the Chas. H Tompkins Co. as builder for the fire towers at the Hospital."
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 12/10/1942 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Text on folder "Resolutions concerning curtailment of note with American Security and Trust Compnay securing Lots 819-823 in Square 210. Grading and surfacing of parking lot. Madeira Apartments. Fire protection for the Hospital. Transfer of $65,307 from general funds to Lisner Fund. Razing of house at 734-23rd Street. Purchase of Lot 17 in Square 56."
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 05/28/1940 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 02/08/1940 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Text on folder "Purchase of Lot 817, Sq. 101 - 21st & H, Lot 830, Sq. 40 - N.H. Ave., Lot 35, Sq. 40 - N.H. Ave."
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 12/12/1939 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Text on folder "(Razing of 2024 & 2026 H. St.; Building 2d floor on Mechanical Eng. Lab.)"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 12/05/1939 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Text on folder "(Sale of Lot 5, Sq. 87 - N.Y. Ave.)"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 03/08/1939 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 01/24/1939 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 10/04/1938 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 01/14/1938 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Text on folder "re: Purchase of lots 802, 803, 4, 812, 814, B in Sq. 79. Lites for Hall of Gov. and Technology"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 12/23/1937 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 12/01/1937 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 05/07/1936 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 04/07/1936 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 10/08/1935 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Text on folder "re: Contract between the university and the architect for the Strong dormitory."
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 08/27/1935 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Text on folder "re: Strong Dormitory"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 04/29/1935 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Text on folder "re: purchase of property next to Business office Strong Dormitory"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 11/30/1934 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    Text on folder "re: new science building"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, 10/21/1934 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Text on folder "re: purposed plan for University Biological Sciences bldg. Site for gymnasium"
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, Committee on the Medical Center, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Committee on Building Lands--meeting minutes, Minutes Prior to 1927, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Committee on Endowment Funds, Correspondence:, 1925 -1954 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Committee on Endowment Funds--meeting minutes, 01/22/1960 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Committee on Endowment Funds--meeting minutes, 04/02/1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Executive Committee, Minutes, 06/26/1939 --03/04/1942 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Executive Committee, Correspondence, general:, 1933 -1965 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Executive Committee--correspondence and meeting minutes, 09/30/1960 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    Text on folder "Approval of final details of the Group Life Insurance Plan. Approval of recommendation extending the time whenproperty may be purchased under Board authority granted February 11, 1960, from August 31, 1960 to October 13, 1960. The Committee adjourned."
  - Executive Committee--correspondence and meeting minutes, 01/22/1960 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    Text on folder "Report by Acting President Colclough concerning the past, present and future of the University. Discussion of financial needs of the University. Adjourment"
  - Executive Committee--correspondence and meeting minutes, 07/16/1959 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    Text on folder "Approval of recommendation of Committee on Buildings and Lands authorizing the Committee to purchase property when available at fair market prices within total expenditure of $400,000 during period ending August 31, 1960. Approval of recommendation of Committee on Finance authorizing the Committee to mortgage University income-producing properties to the extent of $400,000 to carry out property acquisition program of the Buildings and Lands Committee."